A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Family and Friends, Series H FA343
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Family and Friends, Series H
1908-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA343
132 document box(es)
Biographical/Historical note
Nelson Aldrich Rockefeller was born on July 8, 1908, in Bar Harbor, Maine, the third child of John Davison Rockefeller, Jr., and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller. He graduated from the Lincoln School of Teachers College at Columbia University in New York City in 1926. Mr. Rockefeller attended Dartmouth College where he was elected to Phi Beta Kappa, graduating cum laude in 1930 with an A.B. degree in economics.
After college, Mr. Rockefeller was active in family enterprises, including real estate, banking, and family philanthropies. His major business interests in time became focused on Rockefeller Center and Latin America. In 1938, he became the president of Rockefeller Center.
In 1935, because of his interest in national affairs and his desire to learn about U.S. business abroad, Mr. Rockefeller became a director of Creole Petroleum Company, the Venezuelan subsidiary of Standard Oil of New Jersey. This association led eventually to his deep, life-long interest in Latin America. He made extensive visits to Latin America in 1937 and 1939 to study economic, social, and political conditions. He resigned his directorship in the Creole Petroleum Company in 1940.
In 1940, Mr. Rockefeller and his four brothers organized the Rockefeller Brothers Fund to carry out a broad range of philanthropic activities.
Throughout his life Mr. Rockefeller was an avid supporter of the arts. He served as a trustee, treasurer, president, and chair of the board of the Museum of Modern Art, which was cofounded by his mother. In 1954, he founded the Museum of Primitive Art, which collected of indigenous art of the Americas, Africa, Oceania, and early Asia and Europe.
After his 1939 visit to Latin America, Mr. Rockefeller prepared a memorandum for President Franklin D. Roosevelt outlining his deep concern over Nazi influence and penetration into that part of the world. In the memo he recommended a U.S. program of cooperation with the nations of the western hemisphere to achieve better relations among these nations and to help raise their standards of living. Largely as a result of this memo, President Roosevelt asked Mr. Rockefeller in August of 1940 to initiate and head a new program ultimately known as the Office of Inter-American Affairs. Mr. Rockefeller served as Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs, his first full-time position in public service.
Mr. Rockefeller served in this position until December 1944, when President Roosevelt appointed him Assistant Secretary of State for American Republic Affairs. In this post, Mr. Rockefeller initiated the Inter-American Conference on Problems of War and Peace in Mexico City in February of 1945. It resulted in the Act of Chapultepec, which provided the framework for economic, social, and defense cooperation among the nations of the western hemisphere and set the principle that an attack on one of these nations would be regarded as an attack on all and jointly resisted.
Mr. Rockefeller signed the Act of Chapultepec on behalf of the United States. He also attended the United Nations Conference on International Organization in San Francisco in 1945. At the conference, there was considerable opposition to the idea of permitting, within the UN Charter, the formation of regional pacts such as the Act of Chapultepec. Mr. Rockefeller, who believed that the inclusion was essential, especially to U.S. policy in Latin America, successfully argued the need for regional pacts within the framework of the United Nations. The importance of this victory was underscored by the subsequent formation of NATO, SEATO, and the Rio Pact.
During these war-time years, Mr. Rockefeller also served as Chairman of the Inter-American Development Commission, which was established in June 1940 to reorganize and revitalize Latin American economies following the loss of European markets. He was also the U.S. Co-Chairman of the Mexican-American Development Commission to help Mexico emerge as an industrial nation in the transition from war to peace.
Mr. Rockefeller resigned as Assistant Secretary of State on August 24, 1945.
Upon his return to private life in New York in 1946, Mr. Rockefeller became chair of the board of Rockefeller Center and undertook a program of physical expansion. Two other initiatives during this period illustrate Mr. Rockefeller's continuing interest in Latin America and international economic development. In July of 1946, the Rockefeller brothers established a philanthropic organization, the American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA). AIA financed nonprofit projects to ameliorate health, educational, agricultural, and other social problems in the poorer areas of Latin America. Nelson Rockefeller served as President from July 1946 to June 1953 and from January 1957 to December 1958. In 1947, he organized the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC), a business corporation to help raise living standards in foreign countries through new economic enterprises. In its early years, IBEC concentrated on enterprises in Latin America but later expanded its activities to other regions. Mr. Rockefeller served as IBEC President from January 1947 to June 1953 and from January 1956 to December 1958.
In his inaugural address in January 1949, President Harry S. Truman announced the Point IV program for providing technical assistance to developing nations. This concept was based in part on programs Mr. Rockefeller and his associates had developed through the Office of the Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs and the private, philanthropic AIA. In November of 1950, President Truman asked Mr. Rockefeller to serve as Chairman of the International Development Advisory Board. The Board was charged with recommending policies for carrying out the Point IV program. The Board's report, entitled "Partners in Progress," provided the basic blueprint for America's foreign assistance program.
On November 20, 1952, President-elect Dwight D. Eisenhower asked Mr. Rockefeller to serve as Chairman of the President's Advisory Committee on Government Organization, a group created to recommend ways to improve the efficiency of the executive branch of the government. As Chairman of that committee, Mr. Rockefeller recommended 13 reorganization plans to the President, 10 of which were approved by Congress. These plans achieved basic changes in the organization of the Department of Defense, the Department of Agriculture, and the Office of Defense Mobilization, among others. Another of the plans led to the establishment of the Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. In June 1953, Mr. Rockefeller was appointed Under Secretary of the new department. He was especially active in the department's legislative program, recommending measures that covered an additional ten million people under the Social Security program. He resigned as HEW Under Secretary in 1954 to become Special Assistant to the President for Foreign Affairs.
While serving as Special Assistant, Mr. Rockefeller played a key role in the development of the "Open Skies" proposal for checking on world armaments through mutual air reconnaissance. He accompanied President Eisenhower to the Geneva Summit Conference in 1955, where the plan was proposed to the world by the President. Mr. Rockefeller resigned as Special Assistant on December 31, 1955.
Mr. Rockefeller first ran for public office in 1958 and was elected Governor of New York on November 4, defeating incumbent Averill Harriman. He took office January 1, 1959, and was subsequently re-elected Governor three more times, thus becoming the first Governor in the nation's history to be elected to four 4-year terms.
Nelson Rockefeller's tenure as a public servant in the federal government was a formative period in his life. By the time he left Washington to assume the governorship of New York, he had received a thorough education in the workings of the federal government. His chairmanship of PACGO permitted him to examine every aspect of the executive branch. This and his work in HEW exposed him to a wide variety of domestic issues. He gained experience in initiating legislation, in foreign policy and diplomacy, in domestic and international economics, and in national security and military affairs. In the process he also received an education in national politics and gained a reputation for being an effective and hardworking administrator. Most importantly, these appointments provided him with the opportunity to form the friendships and personal associations that served him throughout his political career.
Mr. Rockefeller resigned as Governor of New York in December 1973. In August 1974, President Gerald R. Ford nominated him to fill the vacant vice presidency following the resignation of President Richard M. Nixon. Mr. Rockefeller served as Vice President from December 19, 1974, to January 20, 1977. Nelson Rockefeller died on January 26, 1979, in New York City.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 04 H
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net wealth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement note
The series begins with files on Nelson Rockefeller's friends, arranged alphabetically by last name, and continues with his files on family members, arranged by generation.
Scope and Contents note
This series contains the personal and office files of Nelson A. Rockefeller specifically related to his family members and friends, dating from Rockefeller's birth in 1908 and continuing through 1973. Usually, the files comprise correspondence with or about these individuals, but newspaper clippings, publications, reports, inventories, notebooks, diaries, and photographs are also included (photographs have been transferred to the photo collection). There are also a number of folders of early materials on Nelson Rockefeller himself, which were most likely kept by his mother and then passed along to him at various times. These range from height charts from his infancy, to school work and bank statements from his adolescence, to clippings on his engagement in 1929. Also among this material are numerous photographs taken by Rockefeller, who in his adolescence had a passion for photography.
The series begins with alphabetically arranged files on Nelson Rockefeller's friends (19.5 boxes). These files include a few distant family members on both the Rockefeller and Aldrich sides. The series then continues with the Rockefeller family (111.5 boxes). The family files are arranged primarily by a combination of generation, chronology, and closeness of relationship. For example, general Rockefeller family materials come first, followed by files on paternal great-grandfather William Avery Rockefeller and then John D. Rockefeller, Sr. The next several boxes document Nelson's youth, adolescence, and college years, which are then followed by materials related to his parents, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller. Nelson's stepmother, Martha Baird Rockefeller, comes next, and then his siblings and their children. After several boxes on Nelson during his adult years are materials on his two wives and descendants.
MATERIALS OF SPECIAL SIGNIFICANCE
Numerous sections of this series contain materials of special significance for research on Nelson Rockefeller, the Rockefeller family, and others. Among correspondents of note are Sherman Adams, Thomas Braden, Ralph Bunche, Dwight D. Eisenhower, Wallace K. Harrison, William and Oveta Hobby, General George C. Marshall, Roberto Montenegro, Eleanor Roosevelt, Edward Stettinius, Henry A. Wallace, and Earl Warren. Within the Rockefeller family portion of this series, the correspondence between Nelson and John D. Rockefeller, Jr., is substantial, dating from as early as 1917 and continuing until his father's death in 1960. In contrast, the series holds only a handful of letters from John D. Rockefeller, Sr.
Several female family members are well documented in this series. Foremost, Rockefeller's close relationship with his mother is evident in their letters, which begin in 1917 and go until 1941. Aunts on both the Aldrich and Rockefeller sides of the family are represented here, as is Martha Baird Rockefeller, his stepmother. Also, correspondence from Mary Todhunter Clark (whom Rockefeller married in 1930) begins in 1926, and among other things, provides insight into his years at Dartmouth College. Lastly, following her passing in 2015, 18 boxes of correspondence and clippings on Margaretta (Happy) Fitler (whom Rockefeller married in 1963) were opened to research. These files date from 1963 to 1972 and document her philanthropic, social, and political activities during his second, third, and fourth terms as governor of New York, as well as her involvement in Rockefeller's campaigns for the Republican presidential nomination in 1964 and 1968.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller papers, Activities (FA338)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, AIA-IBEC (FA339)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Art (FA340)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Countries (FA341)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, DNA (FA342)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Oral Histories (FA344)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Politics - New York City Office (FA345)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Politics - George L. Hinman (FA346)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Politics - Oscar M. Ruebhausen (FA347)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Projects (FA348)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Speeches, Post-Vice Presidential (FA349)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Washington, DC (FA350)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Ann C. Whitman - Politics (FA351)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Papers, Hugh Morrow Interviews (FA352)
International relations -- United States; Latin America; Agriculture; Agriculture -- Latin America; Art, Primitive; Brazil; Business; Education; Venezuela; Rockefeller family
- Adams, Sherman (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Albright, Horace (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Aldrich, Nelson - Ancestry (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Aldrich, Nelson - Papers (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Aldrich Family - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Aldrich, Lucy - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Aldrich, Lucy - Death (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Aldrich, Lucy - Estate Distribution (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Aldrich, Lucy - Estate Distribution (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Aldrich, Mr. and Mrs. Winthrop (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Aldrich, Winthrop - Apartment on Fifth Avenue (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Aldrich, Winthrop - Latin America (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Aldrich, Winthrop - Latin America Lists, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Aldrich, Winthrop - Latin America - Turnbull Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Aldrich, Winthrop - Latin America - Oreamuno Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Andrade, Victor - Trip Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Andrade, Victor - Memos, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Andrade, Victor - Report Extracts, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Andrade, Victor - Report #1 Mexico, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Andrade, Victor - Report #2 Venezuela, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Andrade, Victor - Report #3 Colombia, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Andrade, Victor - Report #4 Ecuador, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Andrade, Victor - Report #5 Peru, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Andrade, Victor - Report #6 Chile, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Andrade, Victor - Report #7 Brazil, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Andrade, Victor - Report #8 Argentina, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Austin, Warren (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Baldwin, Joseph Clark (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Bates, Ana (Tia) (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Benton, William, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Benton, William, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Benton, William, 1949-1957 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Benton, William - Foxhall Lease (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Benton, William, 1959-1968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Bering, Dr. and Mrs. E. (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Berle, Adolf (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Berle, Beatrice (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Borella, Victor (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Borella, Victor (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Bowler, Helen Rockefeller (John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s cousin) (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Boyer, Louise (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Braden, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Braden, Thomas - Blade-Tribune Stock Transfer (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Bunche, Dr. Ralph J. (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Carson, Robert (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Chandler, Si (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Chase, Frederick and Virginia (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Clark, John McLane (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Clayton, William (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Corrigan, Frank (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Corry, Andrew (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Creel, Dana - Items Collected by (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Davis, Frederick (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Dilworth, J. Richardson (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Dodge, Geraldine Rockefeller (John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s cousin) (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Donnelly, Walter J. (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Dorsey, Fisher (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Ebenstein, Samuel (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Eisenhower, Dwight D. - Memos for NATO Meeting, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Employees (CLOSED FOLDERS)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restriction-Confidential material
- Ferrer, Mel and Audrey Hepburn (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Finley Award - Recipients of (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Fisher, Raymond (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Fisher, Sterling (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Frank, Waldo (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Friele, Berent
  - 1941-1953 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - 1953-1966 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - 1967-1970s (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Latin American Memos (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Dean Rusk Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Foreign Visitors (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Foreign Visitors (Box 8, Folder 0082A)
    Restricted material
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Mrs. Alexander Grieg Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 84)
- French, Mary Billings
  - General (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Diary Volume II (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Diary Volume IV (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Diary Volume V (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Diary Volume VII (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Diary Volume IX (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Diary Volume XI (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Diary Volume XII (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Diary Volume XIII (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Diary Volume XIV (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Diary Volume XV (Box 9, Folder 95)
- Gallivan, Jack (Box 9, Folder 96)
- Gaudet, William (Box 9, Folder 97)
- Grant, Edwin (Box 9, Folder 98)
- Griffing, Dr. John ("Dad") (Box 9, Folder 99)
- Guille Brown, Helen Tucker (cousin) (Box 9, Folder 100)
- Guille Cary Brown, Helen Tucker (cousin) (Box 9, Folder 101)
- Gumbel, Robert (Box 9, Folder 102)
- Haffenreffer, Carl (Box 9, Folder 103)
- Harris, Paul, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 104)
- Harrison, Sarah M. - Trust Fund - Power of Attorney and Trustees (Box 9, Folder 105)
- Harrison, Wallace K., 1936-1945 (Box 10, Folder 106)
- Harrison, Wallace K., 1947-1967 (Box 10, Folder 107)
- Harrison, Wallace K. - Book Idea, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 108)
- Harrison and Abramovitz (Box 10, Folder 109)
- The Wallace K. Harrison Book, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 110)
- Herter, Christian A. (Box 10, Folder 111)
- Hickery, Margaret (Box 10, Folder 112)
- Hinman, George L. (Box 10, Folder 113)
- Hobby, William and Oveta (Box 10, Folder 114)
- Hoffman, Paul (Box 10, Folder 115)
- Hoffman, Paul - Book Manuscript (Box 10, Folder 116)
- Hood, Harvey (Box 10, Folder 117)
- Jamieson, Frank - General (Box 11, Folder 118)
- Jamieson, Frank - Condolences (Box 11, Folder 119)
- Jofre, Bernardo (Box 11, Folder 120)
- Jones, Nina (Box 11, Folder 121)
- Kanzler, Ernest (Box 11, Folder 122)
- Karsh, Youses (Box 11, Folder 123)
- Keebler, Philip (Box 11, Folder 124)
- Keppel, Charles (Box 11, Folder 125)
- Keppel, Charles - Requests (Box 11, Folder 126)
- Keppel, Charles - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Museum of Primitive Art (MoPA) (Box 11, Folder 127)
- Keppel, Charles - Memos to Louise Boyer (Box 11, Folder 128)
- Klebba, A. Joan (Box 11, Folder 129)
- Krogstad, Anne-Marie Rusmussen Rockefeller (Former Daughter-in-Law) (Box 11, Folder 130)
- La Chaise, Mrs. Gaston (Box 12, Folder 131)
- LaFollette, Charles and Lala (Box 12, Folder 132)
- Lang, Otto (Box 12, Folder 133)
- Lindsay, Frank and Louise (Box 12, Folder 134)
- Lloyd, Stacy (Box 12, Folder 135)
- Lockwood, John (Box 12, Folder 136)
- Lopez Contreras, Gen. and Mrs. Eleazar (Box 12, Folder 137)
- Mrs. Lopez Contreras - Luncheon (Box 12, Folder 138)
- Mrs. Lopez Contreras - Dinner, June 25, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 139)
- Mrs. Lopez Contreras - Dinner - Photos, June 25, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 140)
- Ludington, Howard (Box 12, Folder 141)
- McCormick, Fowler (cousin) (Box 13, Folder 142)
- McGregor, Austen (Sandy) (Box 13, Folder 143)
- McLaughlin, J. Frank (Box 13, Folder 144)
- Marini, Marino (Box 13, Folder 145)
- Marshall, Gen. George C. (Box 13, Folder 146)
- Martin, William (Box 13, Folder 147)
- Miller, Edward G., Jr. (Box 13, Folder 148)
- Milton, David (former brother-in-law) (Box 13, Folder 149)
- Mintener, Bradshaw (Box 13, Folder 150)
- Mirick, Dr. Gordon (Box 13, Folder 151)
- Mitchell, Donna (Box 13, Folder 152)
- Montague, Gilbert (Box 13, Folder 153)
- Montenegro, Roberto, 1940s-1954 (Box 14, Folder 154)
- Montenegro, Roberto, 1955-1968 (Box 14, Folder 155)
- Neylar, John Travers (Box 14, Folder 156)
- O'Brien, John J. ("Cap") (Box 14, Folder 157)
- O'Brien, John J. ("Cap") (Box 14, Folder 0157A)
- Office Space - Rockefeller Center (Box 14, Folder 159)
- Office Operations Committee (Box 14, Folder 160)
- O'Neil, James E. (Box 15, Folder 178)
- O'Neill, Charles (Box 15, Folder 179)
- Abby R. Milton O'Neill (niece), 1949-1969 (Box 15, Folder 180)
- Abby R. Milton O'Neill (niece), 1949-1969 (Box 15, Folder 180a)
  Conditions Governing Access Note
- Oser, Peter (cousin's son) (Box 15, Folder 181)
- Packard, Arthur W. - Files (Box 16, Folder 182)
- Paley, William S. (Box 16, Folder 183)
- Palmer, Thomas W. (Box 16, Folder 184)
- Parkhurst, Richard (Box 16, Folder 185)
- Parran, Thomas (Box 16, Folder 186)
- Paterson, Chat (Box 16, Folder 187)
- Patterson, Mr. and Mrs. Robert P. (Box 16, Folder 188)
- Perkins, Milo (Box 16, Folder 189)
- Perkins, Roswell B. (Box 16, Folder 190)
- Pineo, Charles C. (Box 16, Folder 191)
- Prentice, Alta Rockefeller (aunt) (Box 16, Folder 192)
- Prentice Family (Box 16, Folder 193)
- Purcell, Robert W. (Box 16, Folder 194)
- Rao, Paul P. (Box 17, Folder 195)
- Reath, Henry T. (Box 17, Folder 196)
- Redmont, Bernard S. (Box 17, Folder 197)
- Reed, Mr. and Mrs. John E. (Box 17, Folder 198)
- Reiber, John M. (Box 17, Folder 199)
- Reston, James (Box 17, Folder 200)
- Ridgway, Gen. Matthew B. (Box 17, Folder 201)
- Riland, Dr. and Mrs. Kenneth (Box 17, Folder 202)
- Ritchie, Mr. and Mrs. Andrew C. (Box 17, Folder 203)
- Robbins, Chancey ("Hutch") (Box 17, Folder 204)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 17, Folder 205)
- Rovensky, Joseph C. (Box 17, Folder 206)
- Ruebhausen, Mr. and Mrs. Oscar M. (Box 17, Folder 207)
- Ruebhausen, Oscar M. - General Memoranda (Box 17, Folder 208)
- Ruebhausen, Oscar M. - Projects (Box 17, Folder 209)
- Ruebhausen, Oscar M. - Property Memoranda (Box 17, Folder 210)